下面是我如何对测试代码进行精简的  我喜欢看到优秀的关于测试的想法
Here 's how I ended up simplifying things. I'd love to see great testing ideas.
如果你对你创造的东西很讲究  可以把它们发布到
So, if you're particular to what you've created, post your solution to
论坛中  我要开始对测试代码进行一些重构的工作了
the forums. I'm starting off refactoring things a little bit. What I'm
我接下来要做的是添加一个获取包含位置信息的ContentValues对象的函数
going to do is I'm going to add a function to get the location ContentValues.
这对我们后面在其它地方使用到这些测试
This will be useful when we actually try to use these tests for
会很有用  这些就是了 一个会返回
some other things later on. And there we are. A function that'll
包含位置信息的ContentValues的函数  另外我要将城市名的变量定义在外面
return location content values. I'm also going to pull the city name out so
这样后面就可以在一些验证步骤中使用到它  就像这样
we can use that for some validation steps later on. And there we are. It's now
我们现在在测试函数中  我们可以直接调用刚才的函数来
inside of the function. And then we're simply going to call that function to
获取包含位置信息的ContentValues对象  这些代码都可以删除了
get our location content values and we can delete all those lines of code.
我之前说过这里的这些列的变量并不是很重要
Now, all of these columns, as I said before, are not very important, so
所以我们可以删除掉  然后在查询的参数中传入null
we can delete them. And we can also null out the value in our query.
我要做的下一件事是修改这个验证步骤  我们可以
The next thing I want to do is actually fix this validation step. What we can do
根据从ContentValues对象中获取到的键值对的集合
is we can create a function that relies on the fact we can get the map and
来创建一个方法  这样我们可以很容易的遍历它们
set from our content values. And then we can simply iterate through those.
然后我们可以看到从cursor对象中返回的值是否和我们用来
Then we can see if the values that we used to create the record actually past
创建记录的值是一样的  现在回到我们的测试中
the values in the cursor that are returned. Now, back to our test. So,
现在这里有很多没有必要的代码  我们需要做的只是使用values和cursor
there's a lot of unnecessary code here now. All we have to do is call
作为参数调用validateCursor()方法  好了  我们已经
validateCursor() with our values and our cursor. All right. So now we've
改好了第一个测试  我们也可以对第二个测试做同样的事情
converted the first test. We can do the same thing with the second test as well.
首先  让我们再做一遍之前所做的抽象的工作  当然了
First of all, let's do the same abstraction we did before. Now, of course,
这里的这些值不会保持不变  所以我们直接添加这些值
one of these values isn't going to be static, so we have to add that in.
现在我们可以这样做  把getWeatherContentValues()返回的对象赋给weatherValues变量
So now we can say, ContentValues equals getWeatherContentValues().
参数传递的是非常重要的locationRowId  记住  表之间是相互关联的
With our all important locationRowId. Remember, our tables are linked.
然后我们可以把这条数据插入数据库  再查询它
And then we can insert it into the database. Query for it.
如果查询成功  我们就又可以通过weatherValues和weatherCursor作为参数调用
If the query is successful we can just call validateCursor() again on our
validateCursor()方法  这样可以减少非常多的代码
weatherValues with our weatherCursor. So much less code.
好了  我们的测试得到大大的精简
And that's it. Our test is vastly simplified and
这会对后面的工作带来帮助  我们现在可以再次运行这个测试
it will be useful to us later on. So now we can try running this test again to
看看它在重构以后还能不能正常工作  结果是测试通过了
see if it still works after the refactoring. And there we are, test passed. Now,
也许多写一些代码可以帮助我们更好地
it'd probably be useful for us to actually print out some more data so
观察测试的内容  但是  这次对测试的精简
we can see what was being tested. But, this simplification to our
在我们进行后面的工作的时候会大有裨益  关于测试的部分我们还没有讲完
test is going to help us as we move forward. We're not done with testing yet.